A Guide to the John K. Martin Records, 1777-1907
Library of Virginia
- Pension Files, 1777-1883 and n.d., 10.62 cubic feet. (Boxes 1-24)
  - War of 1812, 1812-1883 and n.d., 6.525 cubic feet. (Boxes 6-20)
    - War of 1812 - Eubank, John-Farguson (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Eubank, Johnson, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Ford, David, 1850-1854 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Fore, Henry, 1852 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Folks, John, 1855 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Faherty, Bartlett, 1851-1852 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Farguson, Darius K., 1855 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Farley-Furgoson (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Farley, Henry, 1851-1855 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Farmer, Benjamin, 1857 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Farmer, Ebenezer, 1852 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Farmer, Mark, 1854 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Farris, Marshall, 1853-1854 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Farris, William, 1878-1879 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Ferguson, Edmund, 1851 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Fergoson, Theodorick, 1854 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Fidler-Folkes (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Fidler, Martin, 1851 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Fields, Frederick, 1856-1857 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Fitzhugh, John, 1880-1881 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Fleming, Anthony, 1854 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Fleming, John, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Flemming, William, 1857 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Folkes, Elijah, 1853, 1878-1879 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Folkes, Joseph, 1856-1857 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Ford-Foscue (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Ford, Frederick A., 1856 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Ford, Henry, 1852 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Ford, Obediah, 1854 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Ford, William, 1853-1854 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Foscue, Benjamin, 1815-April 1881 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Foscue, Benjamin, May 1881-1882 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Foster-Fowler (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Foster, Anthony, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Foster, Blackwell, 1855 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Foster, Daniel, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Foster, Thomas, 1851, 1855 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Foster, Weldon Goode, 1858-1859, 1882 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Fowler, Fountain, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Fowler, Jeremiah, 1878 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Fowler, King, 1851-1852 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Francis-Franklin (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Francis, Peter, 1856-1857 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Francisco, James, 1851-1852 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Franklin, Jesse, 1881 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Franklin, Thomas, 1852 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Franklin, William, 1851 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Freeze-Froman (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Freeze, Jacob, 1881-1882 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Fretwell, John, 1853-1854 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Froman, John, 1851-1852 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Fry-Fuguo (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Fry, John, 1879-1880 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Fugua, Irby, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Fugua, Samuel, 1855 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Fuguo, Joshua, 1855, 1859 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Fulks-Gary (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Fulks, Pleasant, 1880 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Gamble, Robert, 1854, 1872 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Gardner, William, 1855, 1871 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Garner, William, 1857-1858 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Garrett, Ira, 1859 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Gary, James, 1854 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Gary, William, 1852-1853 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Gallaher-Gennett (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Gallaher, John S., 1877 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Gates, William, 1878-1879 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Gay, Edward S., 1878-1879 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Gay, Neil B., 1854 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Gee, Henry, 1873, 1878-1879 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Gennett, Armistead, 1829, 1853 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Gentry-Gibbs (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Gentry, Harmon H., 1851-1852 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Gentry, Wyatt, 1856 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - George, David, 1882 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - George, William, 1878-1880 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Gibbs, Charles, 1879-1880 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Gibbs, Samuel, 1853 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Gibson-Giles (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Gibson, Stephen, 1878 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Gibson, William E., 1853, 1879 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Gifford, William, 1814 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Giles, Thomas, 1856 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Giles, William, 1851-1852, 1880-1881 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Gill-Glass (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Gill, Bolling, 1879 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Gill, Nathaniel, 1853, 1857 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Gill, Rowitt, 1866-1879 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Gill, William, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Glass, Thomas, 1878-1879 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Godsey-Goff (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Godsey, Thomas O., 1875-1882 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Godfrey, Zachariah, 1818 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Godsey, Solomon, 1857, 1879 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Goff, William, 1851 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Goff, Zachariah, 1854-1856 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Golliver-Goolsby (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Golliver, John, 1879-1881 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Goodman, Richard, 1858 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Goode, Mark, 1878-1880 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Goolsby, N. O., 1880-March 1881 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Goolsby, N. O., April 1881-1882 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Gordon-Graves (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Gordon, John L., 1881 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Gordon, Thomas H., 1881 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Gordon, William, 1856 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Gossett, John, 1882 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Goudy, Edmund, 1850, 1854 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Grasty, George, 1879 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Graves, Bartholomew, 1853 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Graves, Ben, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Graves, Crosher, 1851-1856 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Graves, John, 1854-1856 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Graves-Green (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Graves, Lewis, 1880-1881 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Graves, Williamson, 1850 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Gray, Alexander M., 1824 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Gray, W. W., 1881 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Green, George, 1878-April 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Green, George, April 1879-December 1880 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Green, George-Green, Joseph (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Green, George, December 1880-September 1881 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Green, George, September 1881-1882 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Green, Joseph, 1856 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Greenway-Guthrie (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Greenway, Joseph, 1854 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Gregg, Henry, 1879-1880 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Gregory, David W., 1879 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Gunter, Jeremiah, 1852, 1855-1856 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Guthrie, Henry P., 1851 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Hair-Hall (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Hair, William, 1878-March 1879 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Hair, William, April 1879-1880 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Hall, Alexander, 1853 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Hall, William J., 1878-1881 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Hall, Jacob-Hancock (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Hall, Jacob, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Hall, John, 1813, 1854-1861 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Hampton, Joshua, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Hancock, Henry, 1852 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Hancock, Higgison, 1852-1853 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Hancock, Jeremiah, 1866 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Hare-Harris, Hiram (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Hare, Wyatt, 1880-1881 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Harlow, Williams, 1852 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Harris, George, 1850-1852 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Harris, Hiram, 1878-1879 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Harris, William-Harrison, Charles (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Harris, William H., 1880 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Harris, [_], 1876-1877 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Harrison, Benjamin M., 1854-1856 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Harrison, Charles, 1879 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Harrison, Charles, 1880-September 1881 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Harrison, Charles-Harrison, William H. (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Harrison, Charles, November 1881-1882 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Harrison, James, 1876-May 1878 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Harrison, James, July 1878-1881 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Harrison, Thomas R., 185- (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Haskins-Hawkins (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Haskins, Creed T., 1851-1853 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Haskins, Robert, 1855-1860 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Hatcher, Charles R., 1852-1856 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Hatcher, William, 1813 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Hawkins, Daniel, 1851-1852 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Hazelgrove-Hewitt (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Hazelgrove, Benjamin, 1856, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Hazelgrove, Pleasant, 1852 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Hefferton, Elijah B., 1854, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Hendree, George, 1851 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Hewitt, Thomas W., 1814? (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Hill-Hitchcock, Higgison (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Hill, John, 1852-1853 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Hill, William, 1853 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Hines, John, 1882 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Hines, Joseph, 1882 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Hinton, William, 1855-1860 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Hitchcock, Higgison, 1852 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Hitchcock, John-Hicks (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Hitchcock, John, 1856-1858 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Hix, Samuel, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Hix, Thomas, 1814 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Hickok, John, 1878-1879 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Hicks, Thomas, 1852-1855 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Hobson-Hollis (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Hobson, Adcock, 1852 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Hobson, James, 1854 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Hobson, John C., 1873 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Hobson, Samuel, 1852-1856 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Hodges, Isam, 1879 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Hollingsworth, John, 1857-1858 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Hollis, Richard, 1852-1853 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Holman-Hough (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Holman, Ethelred, 1856 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Holman, William, 1851 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Holman, William M., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Holt, Edwards, 1856 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Holt, George, 1879 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Hooper, James, 1857 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Horner, Benjamin, 1855-1856 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Hough, John, 1879 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - House-Howell (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - House, Richmond W., 1855 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Howard, George, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Howard, John, 1877-1878 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Hoye, James, 1854-1860 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Howard, James, 1853-1856 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Howell, Spicer, 1876-1878 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Huckstep-Humphrey, Isiah (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Huckstep, John, 1855 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Hudson, Christopher, 1850-1857 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Huff, Powell H., 1850-1851 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Hughson, N., 1851 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Hume, Jacob or Robert? 1873, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Humphrey, Isaiah, 1853 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - War of 1812 - Humphrey, William-Jackson, Clement (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Humphrey, William, 1851-1853 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Hunter, Samuel, 1857 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Hupp, George Franklin, 1878-1879 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Irby, Douglas, 1852-1853 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Iron, John, 1876 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Isenberser, Henry, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Jackson, Clement, 1878-March 1880 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - War of 1812 - Jackson, Clement-Jamison (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Jackson, Clement, March 1880-1881 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Jackson, Price, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Jackson, Thomas, 1871 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Jamison, John, 1811-1814, 1853-1854 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - War of 1812 - Jarvis-Jett (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Jarvis, Colin, 1837, 1852, 1854 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Jefferson, Thomas, 1875 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Jennings, William, 1872-1873 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Jeter, Samuel, 1855-1856 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Jett, Thornton, 1880 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Johnson, Anderson-Johnson, John (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Johnson, Anderson, 1878 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Johnson, Anthony K., 1853 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Johnson, Charles, 1873 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Johnson, Daniel, 1851, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Johnson, Hugh, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Johnson, James, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Johnson, John, 1853, 1879 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Johnson, Joseph-Johnson, Watson (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Johnson, Joseph, 1852 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Johnson, Martin, 1876 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Johnson, Randolph, 1866-1867 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Johnson, Samuel, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Johnson, Thomas, 1850 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Johnson, Watson, 1851, 1878 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Jones, Ebenezer-Jones, Richard (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Jones, Ebenezer, 1853 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Jones, Edward W., 1854, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Jones, Gilliam, 1859, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Jones, James W., 1878 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Jones, Joseph P., 1853 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Jones, Richard, 1852-1879 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Jones, Robert-Judkins (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Jones, Robert, 1855-1856, 1877 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Jones, Russell, 1879 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Jones, William, 1876 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Jones, William A., 1880-1882 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Jordan, Charles, 1878 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Jordan, William, 1853-1854 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Joyner, William M., 1856 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Jude, Thomas, 1852-1856 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Judkins, Joseph P., 1856 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Keeney-Kimbrough, John P. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Keeney, Daniel, 1856, 1858 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Kelley, Wilson, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Kent, William, 1854 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Keran, Thomas, 1852 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Kersey, Thomas, 1856-1857 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Kesler, Henry, 1879 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Kimbrough, John P., 1873-1874 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Kimbrough, William J.-Knight (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Kimbrough, William J., 1851, 1874 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Kincaid, William, 1880 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Klein, Jacob, 1878 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Knight, Thischarmus, 1845, 1878 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Lacy-Leadbetter (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Lacy, Pleasant, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Lain, Wilson, 1853-1854 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Lamb, Mathew, 1858 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Lancaster, George, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Lanier, William S., 1853-1854 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Lawler, John, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Lawson, Fabias, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Layne, Archer, 1854 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Leadbetter, Isaac, 1873-1880 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Lee-Libby (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Lee, John, 1879 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Lee, W. L., 1881 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - LeSueur, Mosby, 1879-1880 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Lester, John, 1851, 1856 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Libby, Samuel, 1856 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Likens-Lovern (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Likens, Leonard, 1879-1880 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Lipscomb, Beverly B., 1853 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Lipscomb, Thornton C., 1852-1853 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Lockett, Cheatham, 1852, 1878-1879 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Loval, Thomas, 1855 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Lovern, James, 1854 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Lovesay-Luttmire (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Lovesay, Travis, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Lowe, Jesse, 1878-1879 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Lucas, John, 1853 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Lucas, John, 1856, 1858 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Lucas, Thomas, 1854-1855 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Luttmire, Henry, 1852, 1878 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Lyddam-McCook (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Lyddam, Patrick, 1874, 1878 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Lyle, John, 1852, 1853 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Lyon, Jacob, 1878 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - McClain, Henry, 1853 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - McClintock, Thomas M., 1881 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - McConnell, Roddy, 1879 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - McCook, Neil, 1852 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - McCook, Thomas, 1851 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - War of 1812 - McGruder-Macon (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - McGruder, Lewis, 1878 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - McLaughlin, George, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - McLaurine, Joseph, 1845 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - McManners, Hartwell, 1878 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Macon, Miles, 1870-1879 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - War of 1812 - Magnos-Mann (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Magnos, Julian, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Maitland, Michael, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Major, Samuel H., 1853-1854 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Mann, Abner B., 1852-1879 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Mann, James, 1853 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - War of 1812 - Manning-Martin, Humphrey H. (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Manning, David, 1853-1856 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Marks, Silas, 1855 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Marshall, John D., 1854-1855 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Martin, Bayley, 1852 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Martin, David, 1856 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Martin, Humphrey H., 1878 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Martin, John-Melvin (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Martin, John, 1853 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Martin, Randolph, 1854 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Martin, William A., 1852 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Mason, William, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Mayo, Philip, 1874-1878 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Meanly, William A., 1878 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Melton, William H., 1860 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Melvin, Hiram, 1853-1854 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Merriman-Miller, Maurice L. (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Merriman, Thomas, 1879 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Merryman, John T., 1853-1855 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Messler, Lucas, 1880 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Michie, [_], 1851 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Miller, Christopher, 1857 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Miller, Henry, 1880 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Miller, John, 1879-1880 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Miller, Maurice L., n.d. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Miller, Melchesedeck (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Miller, Robert R. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Miller, Thomas-Montague, Henry B. (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Miller, Thomas, 1857-1860 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Mills, John Nicholas, 1877 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Mills, Richard C., 1852-1855 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Miracle, Abraham, 1858 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Mitchell, Abner, 1855 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Mitchell, John, 1851, 1855 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Moncure, John, 1874-1880 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Montague, Henry B., 1852 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Montague, William L.-Moore (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Montague, William L., 1853 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Montell, John, 1855-1857 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Moore, Jeptha, 1881 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Moore, John W., 1860 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Moore, William, 1876 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Moore, William, 1876 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Morgan-Morris, Thomas S. (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Morgan, John S., 1850 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Morris, John, 1856-1857, 1881 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Morris, Samuel F., 1878-1881 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Morris, Thomas S., 1852 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Morris, William-Moseley, Hardaway (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Morris, William, 1851-1857 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Morrison, John, 1878-1879 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Morrissett, David, 1853 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Moseley, Edward H., 1854-1869 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Moseley, Hardaway, 1855 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Moseley, James-Muse (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Moseley, James, 1853 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Moseley, William, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Moses, Samuel F., 1855 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Moss, Isam, 1881 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Moss, William, 1855 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Moyer, Jack, 1881-1882 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Muse, Meredith, 1852 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Myrick-Newby (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Myrick, Walter, 1878 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Nash, James, 1852, 1857 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Nash, Joseph, 1852 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Nash, Reuben, 1878 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Neighbours, Robert R., 1852 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Newby, Abraham, 1852-1853 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Newlan-Newman (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Newlan, David, 1878-1879 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Newman, Robert L., 1859-1870 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - War of 1812 - Nichols-Norville (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Nichols, Daniel, 1874, 1877 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Nichols, Michael, 1857 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Nicholson, Thomas, 1882 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Norris, Richard, 1857 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - North, J. A., 1878 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - North, William, 1852 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Norville, James B., 1855 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Nunnally-Overby (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Nunnally, Claiborne P., 1866 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Nunnally, Edward, 1878-1879 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - O'Connor, Maurice, 1853 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - O'Neal, Thomas, 1860 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Orange, Lewis, 1851-1855 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Organ, Daniel P., 1855 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Overby, John, 1856 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Overby, Obediah-Pare (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Overby, Obediah, 1851, 1881-1882 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Overton, Benjamin, 1854 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Overton, Moses, 1853 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Pagand, Lewis, 1853-1854 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Palmer, Charles, 1854-1855 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Pare, John, 1878-1879 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Parker-Patram, Ben A. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Parker, Jabez, 1878 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Parkhill, John, 1853, 1855 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Parr, Jordan, 1873 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Parrish, Sterling, 1855 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Patmon, William, 1856 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Patram, Ben A., 1851-1852, 1878 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Patram-Payne, Benjamin (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Patram, Francis, 1853, 1878 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Patram, George, 1852-1853 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Patton, James, 1856 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Patterson, Daniel, 1875-1876 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Patterson, James H., 1852 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Payne, Benjamin D., 1852-1860 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Payne, William-Pearman (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Payne, William, 1860-1875 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Payne, William, 1876-1878 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Pearman, Fauntleroy, 1855 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Pearson-Peatross (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Pearson, George, 1876-1880 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Peatross, James W., 1855, 1878-1880 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Peck-Pemberton (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Peck, J. B., 1813-1859 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Peck, John H., 1878 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Pears, Alexander M., 1853-1854 (Box 15, Folder 8)